Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep
within your dreams Taking aim
for your heart so it would
seem Stand tall and read,
go to hell and jump for
paradise Every time dangerous,
dangerous We like it serious, serious,
oh Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today
Adventure calls now,
let's go The balls filled between us, they
will show Still what we don't know Yes,
working hard together Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
Despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through We're living in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers
All the love and the tears
In the world we're in
United gently bringing
up Our thought again,
yeah We're the foolish ones
we love, we'll carry on
Till we see the light, the sun will rise
The greatest fight at its core Is against
myself forevermore Come
on let's do it now,
let's go The balls filled between us,
they will show So what we don't know,
that's what we call adventure Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers
Superpowers Yes, we've got superpowers
Superpowers
Yes, we've got superpowers
Superpowers Yes, we're the superpowers.
Superpowers.
Yes, we're the superpowers.
But it's yours! Yes, sir!
We're all out of the way!
Excellent work, Patakori, sir!
A splendid victory!
Of course, your win was
inevitable from the start!
Though we were concerned, you might not
be able to eat today's snack in a time.
But we've been ready and waiting
patiently since 3 o 'clock, as always!
We are aware of your strict commitment to
holding your merienda at
the same time each day.
We extend our sympathies.
Your tea, most unfortunately, has
become cold in the last 40 minutes.
Ice tea is fine.
Oh, how considerate of him!
We are extremely proud of
the sweets prepared today.
I think you'll find the
selection most appropriate.
That is to say, for a
man as perfect as you,
each treat is made from
the perfect ingredients!
We purchased the finest Carol
cacao we could find on the Black
Market and combined it with milk
from cow grazed on the Sky Island,
whose life was free from stress and woe.
The resulting chocolate is rich and
ideal to dollop atop this giant donut.
And for this one, we whipped
the highest grade cream,
which we received fresh from
the great Minister Abra himself.
Enjoy the sublime sweetness
of all of you and you alone.
I expended a tremendous amount of
Haki in the battle with Straw Hat.
If I intend to subdue his crew,
which is currently on the run,
I need to take in a substantial
amount of nourishment.
Sugar shall provide me with that power.
The feast begins.
I
don't
know.
I will enter the shrine. Sir!
Don't let anyone disturb me.
Of course not.
We shall leave you to your nuts of dough.
Take your time, sir.
Ah, he's as particular as ever. Mm-hmm.
It's not just us.
They say no one has ever caught
him in the act of eating.
He's ceaselessly vigilant and can't
let his guard down even during a snack.
A pity since the whole point of
tea time is to unwind with friends.
But for him,
it's a joyless act of nutritional intake
and solemn meditation
before his next battle.
That's what it means to be a
warrior worth over a billion.
Backbone of the Big Mama Pirates.
Straw Hat couldn't even
lay a finger on the man.
But no surprise there, he
could never stack up. What?
Something wrong?
It's more like something's missing.
Like what?
Stroke hat's a hand.
That's not normal.
Mamma mia.
The mochi, it's jiggling.
Yeah, I can see that.
The question is why?
How would I know?
Stroke hat!
I thought you were dead.
How did you get out of that mochi?
I ate a whole bunch, that's how! What?
Do I gotta eat every time I
have a fight in this dumb place?
The food doesn't even taste good!
Why would you even think to do that?
Sorry kid, you took too
long so he decided to split.
He already loves the
mirror world, in a hurry!
He has important business today, and
come to think of it, so do we. So long!
I sent the voice of
someone strong over there!
Oh, crap!
Observation, Haki!
And he's eating donuts, too!
Haki again?
No, he just smells it.
That jerk!
He's probably celebrating thinking he won!
He will never!
Especially not after an
easy victory like that!
He is meditating!
Communing with the God of War spirit in
a solemn ceremony of the utmost dignity!
It's like a religious experience for him.
No one can be allowed to... intrude?
What's he doing?
Hey!
Where are you going?
After all of that, he
got scaled and ran away.
Can you blame him?
What do you expect from such
a weaker group of pirates?
Let him run.
He won't get far.
Is he coming back?
Why?
I kept running till I got skinny! Huh?
That's not how the body works!
All right, Mock Mochi Man,
I'm back for round two!
Are you ready?
Please, no!
Please, stop this ride!
It's up limits and go away!
Don't go near it!
Come, come!
I'm back, come!
We failed you, General
Katakuri! I'm sorry!
Oh, and donuts.
I love to eat donuts.
I believe in the hosetree.
Donuts.
A snack attack. Donuts.
Lying on my back. Donuts.
A forbidden sweet always
knocks me off my feet.
Doughnuts!
This is my secret garden,
filled with doughnuts!
Doughnuts!
More doughnuts!
No judgement, just...
Doughnuts!
My dad...
My brother's more than strong.
He's undefeated, unbeatable!
He's never lain down and never
been knocked down either.
Why, he's downright
disrespectful to the ground.
His bearing is always noble,
cool-headed and strong.
There's not a single flaw about him.
That's our big brother,
the man you dare to face!
How dare you?
Nobody is allowed to
disturb me while I eat.
Too bad!
This fight isn't over!
Have mercy on me, Kanagore, sir.
I didn't see it.
I didn't see anything.
I won't tell a soul, even if they
try to rip the words from my mouth.
What did you say about my mouth?
That's mochi.
So you're alive.
Forgive me for not seeing
your death through.
But I couldn't wait any longer.
Did you think there was only
one level of armament, Haki?
My strength exceeds yours in every way.
You are nothing but an insect to me!
All who see my true
self must pay the price.
You can't be allowed to live.
Damn it!
He didn't move.
Something's different.
What changed?
What difference will one kick make?
Dodging that was easier.
And that attack was late?
Your ability.
I think I get it now.
There's nothing to get.
Your powers are inferior to mine.
How many times do I have to tell you?
This is it.
I won't hurt my eyes, until
I witness your final breath!
Forgiven!
RAINFALL EMOTION!
You're strong as hell, but not invincible!
Screw you, Straw Hat!
Now, I'll crush you!
Now, come, come!
Tom, run!
I thought I'd never hit you!
Armament should always land,
even against Logia-types.
So when my attacks didn't hit, it
seemed like you were invincible.
Like somehow you were
breaking all the rules.
That wasn't right!
You can get hit like anyone else!
I'll show you! No!
Even defending with your armament hook!
When I use my fourth
gear, I break through!
So now, Gum-Gum!
Culmarin!
It's not your mochi powers
that make you strong!
It's your observation, Haki!
Crom-Crom!
Rhino!
Snyder!
My brother is more than
just strong, you know.
A warrior of superhuman talent who's never
fallen on his back a
single day in his life.
You're more astute than you look.
You've figured me out.
My mochi abilities allow me to
change shape and dodge efficiently.
Observation Haki.
That's my true strength.
I admit, I lost my cool just now.
That's what gave you the
opportunity to strike.
Observation Haki requires a clear
head and a calm heart to utilize.
How long has it been
since I was last punched?
At first,
I found it hard to believe that someone
like you could defeat my brother Cracker.
But now, I'm beginning to see it.
You mean the biscuit guy?
Unstoppable donuts!
Donuts aren't even mochi!
Give me a break, cheater!
Power monkey!
I won't give you another itch.
We're going back to square one.
Please!
I'm begging you!
Open the door and let me inside!
I'm sorry, Mr.
Pound, but we can't allow that.
I'm gonna need you to step back.
Why are you being so cruel to me?
Lady Pudding gave us strict orders.
Come on, I just want to see chiffon,
even if it's just for a little bit.
Who's that big guy?
He's Mama's 25th ex-husband. Oh.
I knew it was her at first class.
She hasn't changed a bit
since the day she was born.
Still cute as ever.
My sweet little girl.
It's been so many years.
Just a minute, a second, as
long as I can see her again.
What's the deal with all that racket?
Just sounds like some guy is yelling.
I wouldn't worry.
Not like they'll be coming in.
What's wrong, Pudding?
It's nothing.
Go ahead, Bear.
What were you just saying?
So,
tomorrow morning at around 1 a .m.,
Straw Hat's ship should be
showing up at Cacao Island,
assuming we don't manage to kill
them before then, of course.
Here?
At 1 a .m.?
The plan was to meet up with the Sunny
at sea and hand over the wedding cake.
What happened?
Why would the Straw Hats
want to come to Kaku Island?
It's simple.
That's where they were planning
to meet up with their captain,
who split up on the rest of the group,
thinking that he could help them escape.
I see.
But if the enemy knows their plan,
this island's going to be
crawling with their soldiers.
The thing is...
Even if they do make it to Kaku Island,
Straw Hat Luffy certainly will not.
And what does that mean?
That he won't be alive.
The idiot pushed his luck and challenged
Big Brother Katakuri to a one-on-one duel.
So you can imagine how
well that's working out.
It serves him right, I say.
All right, heave home!
It's four o 'clock now.
That means in about nine hours,
the Straw Hats will arrive
at Kaku Island and wait
for their precious captain
who will never appear.
Mama still suffering from hunger pangs and
Press will show up around the same time.
Everyone will be gathered
to see the big show.
Needless to say, we can't
afford for anything to go wrong.
We're counting on you to
take care of Mama Pudding.
You're our only hope.
Don't worry, sis. I've got this.
If Mama wants the greatest wedding
cake ever, then that's what she'll get.
I'll look forward to it then.
Oh, by the way, if the Straw Hats happen
to arrive ahead of time, don't worry.
Oven just showed up with his troops.
They'll take care of things for you. What?
Did you say that Oven's here already?
What do you mean I can't enter
the damn factory right now?
That's, uh, Lake Pudding's
order, I'm afraid.
I'm her brother.
I'm sorry, sir.
Well, if she's that insistent,
then I will honor the request.
But if the factory is supposed to
be off limits, then why the crowd?
Oh, uh, yes, it's about that.
Hey!
Come on!
So it's you.
Why are you hurting me?
I'm no threat.
Because you're a damn stalker.
How could you say that?
Don't you remember me, Oven?
Of course I remember you.
You used to be my stepfather.
I'm glad you haven't forgotten.
I know it's been a long time now.
But if you understand my situation, then
maybe you could stop punching me, please.
I'm afraid that you've got this backwards.
Huh?
It's a lot of noise.
I hope it's not a problem.
He just got a pig.
Sanji, are you listening? To your call?
Your captain's in big trouble.
Eh, he'll be fine.
What do you mean?
Challenging Katakuri to a
duel is insanely reckless.
Sounds like Luffy.
Katakuri's bounty is over a billion.
His strength's superhuman next to Luffy.
Big Brother has never lost a
single fight in his entire life.
Then it's a special occasion.
He's about to lose for the first time.
We just need to do our part.
And that's making the
greatest wedding cake ever.
Your captain is as good as dead.
No one has ever defeated Katakuri,
and he's not about to lose to some
lame-ass pirate crew like yours.
Cue that, Sanji.
Relax, Pudding.
Just focus on work.
We've got this.
Let's have fun.
I'm glad we get to do a project together.
Sanji!
Does she have a fever?
Maybe someone baked her?
Not likely!
Lady Pony!
Guess nobody's coming after us.
Something must be amiss.
They'd surely send pursuers
by now if they were able to.
You think something happened then?
I wonder if this is a trap.
Don't worry, Nami.
I promise that we won't let our
guard down even for a second.
That reminds me.
I hope Aladdin and the
others escaped here safely.
Perhaps they were able to
slip away in the chaos.
What did you say?
Briss, I thought Mama was
supposed to be chasing Straw Hats.
Why is she wrecking Nuts Island?
It's not my fault.
Excuse me, Mandor.
I have bad news.
Oh, bad news, you say?
Don't have enough of that, now do we?
We scanned all of the waters nearby.
We searched for the slugs, but...
The thing is...
WHAT?!
What do you mean that all of
the territory slugs are gone?!
Where did they go?!
You don't suppose they're dead, do you?
There's not a single one left!
But there's thousands of them!
They can't all disappear at
once without a single trace!
Maybe someone kidnapped them?
How would they pull that off?
Anyway, we can't have enemy
ships running wild out there!
Go and fix this now!
Um, I can try, but how?
Just find out why they're gone, you idiot!
Get moving! Yasuie, sir!
Sea slugs, why don't you sing with me?
Everyone, be carefree.
Take the day off.
You've worked hard enough.
We'll all have fun, you'll see.
Security, let it be.
Transmitting, now is the time to play.
All day!
Now doesn't this feel so heavenly?
So you see, it's better to be lazy.